{
    "subject": "resource/Silapathar",
    "predicate": "http://www.georss.org/georss/point",
    "object": "27.595277777777778 94.72",
    "human_readable": "Silapathar is located at coordinates (27.595277777777778, 94.72).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9074364900588989,
            "question": "Where is Silapathar located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.891237199306488,
            "question": "What are the coordinates of Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8815723657608032,
            "question": "Give the coordinates for Silapathar."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8366150856018066,
            "question": "Can you provide the specific location of Silapathar using its coordinates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8216022253036499,
            "question": "What is the latitude of Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8210594058036804,
            "question": "How would you express the location of Silapathar using coordinates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.793753981590271,
            "question": "At what latitude and longitude is Silapathar situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7594601511955261,
            "question": "Silapathar's geographic coordinates are given as a pair of numbers. What do these numbers represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7372929453849792,
            "question": "What is the longitude of Silapathar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5502706170082092,
            "question": "What are the numerical values representing Silapathar's geographical position?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Silapathar is located at coordinates (27.595277777777778, 94.72).",
            "html": "dbpedia_689_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the longitude of Silapathar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_689_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Silapathar's geographic coordinates are given as a pair of numbers. What do these numbers represent?",
            "html": "dbpedia_689_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=At what latitude and longitude is Silapathar situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_689_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_689_72.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that Silapathar's coordinates are 26.206, 93.8095.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide the geographical coordinates for Silapathar as (26.206, 93.8095) in some of the files and (27.59441, 94.72402) in others. These do not match the provided coordinates (27.595277777777778, 94.72). Therefore, the triple is incorrect according to the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}